{"data":[{"question":"This is ___ school-bag.","a":"sister's Linda","b":"sister Linda","c":"sister Linda's","d":"sister's Linda's","answer":"3","explain":"- Sister Linda's school bag: shool-bag of a sister who names Linda","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Go and have ___ before we set out.","a":"the sleep","b":"some sleeps","c":"a good sleep","d":"sleep","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We often say \" have a sleep\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Mother does most of ___ at home.","a":"clean","b":"clear","c":"cleaning","d":"the cleaning","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We often say: Someone do the cleaning","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The flight attendants were busy making ___ for the historic flight to that country.","a":"preparations","b":"preparation","c":"preparing","d":"a preparation","answer":"1","explain":"- Preparations [plural]: arrangements for something that is going to happen","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"___ is a big cheat.","a":"That friend of James","b":"That friend of James's","c":"That James friend","d":"That Jame's friend","answer":"2","explain":"- Double possessive:\n\n+ That's friend of James's = that's friend of James, however it stresses the ownership of James\n\n+ That's friend of James: gives more stress on the friend","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Gold is more valuable than ___.","a":"Iron","b":"Irons","c":"The iron","d":"An iron","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Iron: unaccountable noun \n- Don't use article (a,an,the) when mentions things in general","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"___ fish are there in that aquarium?","a":"How many","b":"How much","c":"What is the number of","d":"Do you know how much","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Fish: countable noun- don't use with how much \n- Plural: Fish or fishes \n- This case \"fish\" is plural-\" what is the number of\" is not correct ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"___ do the poor family need for the winter?","a":"How many food","b":"How many foods","c":"How much food","d":"How much of food","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Food: countable and uncountable noun \n- In this case food is uncountable noun= don't use with how many ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"They are ___.","a":"mathematic students","b":"mathematics student","c":"mathematics students","d":"students in mathematics","answer":"4","explain":"- Adjective of mathematics is mathematical (not mathematic)\n\n- We can use \"students in mathematics\", but it's more usual if we say \"mathematic students\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"What does that guy think of the ___?","a":"sports car","b":"sport car","c":"cars sports","d":"car's sport","answer":"1","explain":"- A sports car (or sportscar or sport car [UK]) is a small, usually two seat, two door automobile designed for high speed driving and maneuverability","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"}]}